CLICK TO CLOSE THIS WINDOW

^^ CLICK OR SWIPE UP TO CLOSE THIS WINDOW ^^

Cart

Search

Call

Search

Menu

Pools

Our pools are made in the USA. Be sure to avoid the low priced Chinese and Japanese pools that are floating around the market. They carry no warranty. Above ground pools come in round and oval shapes and are made from a wide variety of material.

Liners

Pool Products

Heating & Solar

Cleaners

Chemicals & Sanitation

Patio & Pool Fun

Lighting & Landscape

Safety & Assist Devices

Winter Items

More ▼

[Search our Site](javascript:$('#search_bar').slideToggle())

[Contact Us](javascript:show_phone())

**Privacy Policy**  
Our Privacy Policy was last updated and posted on January 6, 2014. It governs the privacy terms of our Website, located at www.nationalpoolwholesalers.com. Any capitalized terms not defined in our Privacy Policy, have the meaning as specified in our Terms of Service.  
  
**Your Privacy**  
Internet Pool Group, LLC follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.  
  
**Definitions**  
"Non Personal Information" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser. It may also include publicly available information that is shared between you and others.  
  
"Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you within our Website. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your name, email address, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.  
  
**Information We Collect**  
Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website.  
  
As a Visitor, you can browse our website to find out more about our Website. You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor.  
  
**Computer Information Collected**  
When you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website. Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information. We also collect the following:  

* **Cookies**  
    Our Website uses "Cookies" to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.  

* **Third Party Tracking Tools**  
    We also use third party tracking tools to improve the performance and features of our Website. These third party tracking tools are designed to collect only Non-Personal Information about your use of our Website. However, you understand that such tools are created and managed by parties outside our control. As such, we are not responsible for what information is actually captured by such third parties or how such third parties use and protect that information.  

* **Automatic Information**  
    We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you're headed when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.  

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use the information we receive from you as follows:  

* **Customizing Our Website**  
    We may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to customize our Website.  

* **Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties**  
    We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to us with regards to our Website (i.e. payment processors, Website hosting companies, etc.);such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.  

* **Data Aggregation**  
    We retain the right to collect and use any Non Personal Information collected from your use of our Website and aggregate such data for internal analytics that improve our Website and Service as well as for use or resale to others. At no time is your Personally Identifiable Information included in such data aggregations.  

* **Legally Required Releases of Information**  
    We may be legally required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process;(b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies;(c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms;(d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members;and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of Internet Pool Group, LLC, our Users, employees, and affiliates.  

**Protecting Your Child's Privacy**  
Our Website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 13 ("Child"), though we realize we may have a Child attempt to make purchases through our Website. We do not verify the age of our Users nor do we have any liability for verifying a User's age. If you are a Child, please seek the permission of a parent or guardian before using our Website.If you are a parent or guardian and believe your Child is using our Website, please contact us to remove your Child's account;we reserve the right to ask you for verification of your relationship to the Child before we honor such a request. If we discover that a Child has created an account on our Website, we will immediately delete the account as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties. However, as parent of such a Child, you understand that you are legally liable for any transactions created by the Child.  
  
**Links to Other Websites**  
Our Website may contain links to other websites that are not under our direct control. These websites may have their own policies regarding privacy. We have no control of or responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. You access such linked Websites at your own risk. These websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should check the privacy policies, if any, of those individual websites to see how the operators of those third-party websites will utilize your personal information. In addition, these websites may contain a link to Websites of our affiliates. The websites of our affiliates are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and you should check their individual privacy policies to see how the operators of such websites will utilize your personal information.  
  
**Our Email Policy**  
Our affiliates and we fully comply with national laws regarding SPAM. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us and/or our affiliates. We agree that we will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission.  
  
**Privacy Policy Updates**  
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine. The method we chose is at our sole discretion. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.  
  
**Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please contact us.  

[**Help**](javascript:toggleLnk('lnk_1'))

[**Keep In Touch**](javascript:toggleLnk('lnk_2'))

[**Quick Links**](javascript:toggleLnk('lnk_3'))

[**Customer Service**](javascript:toggleLnk('lnk_4'))

Additional shipping charges for AK, HI and areas that require ferry service or other service charges.

Some restrictions may apply. Not responsible for typographical errors.

© 2024 Internet Pool Group, LLC. All rights reserved[.](javascript:$('.paynav4').show())

Network Error!

There does not appear to be an Internet connection.  
  
Please ensure you are connected to the Internet and try processing your request again.

OK

Loading Error!

There appears to have been a problem trying to process your request. Please try again.

OK

Liner Purchase Issue!

This liner size is only allowed to be purchased at the present time with a swimming pool due to lack of inventory available nationally.  
  
Once more product arrives in August, we may be able to sell them as stand-alone liners again.  
  
In order to sell a pool, it needs a liner, so we must retain a certain number of liners to sell with the pools we have in our warehouse.

OK

Close

We price match our competition!  

SPRING SAVINGS!  

Code: SPRING-1 Save $3 off an order of $75 or more

Code: SPRING-2 Save $5 off an order of $150 or more

Code: SPRING-3 Save $10 off an order of $300 or more

Code: SPRING-4 Save $20 off an order of $600 or more

Code: SPRING-5 Save $40 off an order of $1200 or more

Code: SPRING-6 Save $80 off an order of $2400 or more

Code: SPRING-7 Save $200 off an order of $4000 or more

Use coupon code at checkout!

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Please confirm this form data is correct. Your rates will return in a few moments.  <br>  <br>The weight may need to be adjusted if you have special order items that will not be shipping with your products from our warehouse. |     |
| Weight: |     |
| Class: |     |
| Origin Zip: | 34974 |
| Destination Zip: |     |
| Use Liftgate: |     |
| Use Residential: |     |

Process

Cancel

An error occured when trying to get your freight quote.  
  
Please try again.  
  
If the problem persists, please contact us at 863-467-7161 so we can address the error and get you the required quote.

OK

An error occured when trying to get your freight quote.  
  
Please try again.  
  
If the problem persists, please contact us at 863-467-7161 so we can address the error and get you the required quote.

OK

An error occured when trying to get your freight quote.  
  
SKU does not exist, is not a ground delivery item or it is a kit and cannot be quoted with this tool.

OK

coupons

 Please fill out the form below and we will have you a reply in no time! We have sales reps standing by to answer your questions!  
  
For faster responses, include your mobile number and check the box to receive your reply via text message as well as email.  

 Yes! Send me a text message update!  

Submit

Cancel

You didn't fill out all of the form fields.  
  
Please fill out all form fields so we can process your request.

OK

An error occured when trying to process your request.  
  
Please try again.  
  
If the problem persists, please contact us at 863-467-7161 so we can address the error and get you the answers you are looking for.

OK

Your request has been sent to our sales team.  
  
We look forward to answering your questions for you shortly.

OK

Close

600

800

Close

Video Load Error

360

480

Close
